

Profile Summary

With years of experience as a programmer, I focus on improving software and guiding global IT teams. As a bridge builder, I aim to transform businesses through effective IT solutions and collaboration.

Languages

Dutch (C2 level) English (C1 level) German (B1 level)

Personal Interests

Home Automation Raspberry pi / Linux / Docker Python development Open-source contributions Renewable energy & Sustainability

Personal Activities

Hiking Indoor Rowing Energy Coach Volunteer

Contact

+31628135526

theo@vandersluijs.nl

in linkedin.com/in/tvandersluijs

github.com/tvdsluijs

https://theovandersluijs.eu

This is the 'TL;DR' of my resume, for my complete resume I would like to refer you to LinkedIn or my resume site.

Theo van der Sluijs

Product Manager / Owner | Agile Coach | Python Developer | Sustainability Advisor 🔭

Paul Krügerstraat 20 4443 AK Nisse, Zeeland / NL

t: +31628135526 | m: theo@vandersluijs.nl | w: https://theovandersluijs.eu

Work Experience

Product Owner / Maxxton / 2023 - Present

Middelburg, NL / Pune, India

Skills: Project Management, Team Leadership, Software Development, Agile Methodologies, Product Owner, DAC7 Legislation

Product Owner / PAY. / 2022 - 2023

Spijkenisse, NL / Enschede, NL

Skills: Project Management, Project Planning, Product Owner, Analytical Skills, Business Analysis, Team Leadership, Agile Methodologies

Project Manager / Operational Lead / XSARUS | Digital Commerce / 2021 - 2022 Middelharnis, NL

Skills: Team Leadership, Project Management, Operations Management, Agile Methodologies, Product Owner

CTO / IT Development Manager / Viterra B.V. / 2017 - 2021

Rotterdam, NL / Chennai, India

Skills: IT Management, Project Management, Project Planning, IT Operations, Team Leadership, Software Development, Agile Methodologies

More work experience can be found on my LinkedIn page www.linkedin.com/in/tvandersluijs

Education

Haagse Hogeschool/TH Rijswijk / 1996 - 2001

VIA, Design and Interaction

MEAO Oude Tonge / 1991 - 1996

Computer Science & Business Administration

Willem van Oranje / 1987 - 1991 MAVO

Technical Skills

Debian, Docker, MySQL, Oracle, SQL, PostgreSQL, Lotus Notes Formulas, LotusScript, ABAPOO, Flex2.0, Product Owner, PDF Form Script, VisualBasic, PHP, ASP Classic, Python, ActionScript, Bash, Raspberry Pi, Home Automation

Certificates

- Professional Scrum Master I
- Professional Scrum Product Owner™ level I
- Senior Executive Management